<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Introduction to psycholinguistics</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Introduction to psycholinguistics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Assessment</title>
      <link>/assessment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/assessment/</guid>
      <description>Course assessmentStudents will be assessed on the basis of the following components:
[30%] One-page summaries of three sessions from the first part of the course. Summaries are to be handed in electronically by the day before the following session at the latest. Summaries will be assessed by the course instructor;
[30%] The presentation of a research paper from the second part of the course. Papers will be presented in small groups (2-4 people, depending on the number of attendants).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Materials</title>
      <link>/materials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/materials/</guid>
      <description>Course materialsThe materials are organized in terms of the individual course sessions. For Part I, they consist of slides, session readings, as well as the session summary, which will be uploaded by the instructor before the following session.
Part I — Foundations of psycholinguistics
Session 1: What is psycholinguistics? What do psycholinguists investigate? (here)
Session 2: Investigating linguistic meaning using psycholinguistic tools (here)
Session 3: Psycholinguistic methods: An overview (here)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Syllabus</title>
      <link>/syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/syllabus/</guid>
      <description>Course syllabusPart I — Foundations of psycholinguistics
Session 1: What is psycholinguistics? What do psycholinguists investigate?
Session 2: Investigating linguistic meaning using psycholinguistic tools
Session 3: Psycholinguistic methods: An overview
Session 4: Investigating language production at the discourse level
Session 5: Investigating language comprehension at the discourse level
Session 6: Investigating the relation between production and comprehension
Session 7: How to read and interpret a scientific paper</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>